{
    "question": "Descriptive tentang aula",
    "attachments": [],
    "answers": [
        {
            "answer": "<span>ruang besar atau pendapa (di gedung sekolah dsb) untuk berapat, mengadakan upacara, dsb<br><br></span>",
            "attachments": []
        },
        {
            "answer": "hall is a room that used for many kinds of activity. like for meeting or workshop<br>",
            "attachments": []
        }
    ],
    "related_questions": [
        {
            "slug": "contoh-text-spoof-pake-twist-falling-into-a-well-dong-306",
            "question": "Contoh text SPOOF pake twist \"falling into a well\" dong :)",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "<span>\nSpoof text: Falling Into a Well</span>\n<span>\n</span>\n\nThere was a man. When he was walking, he fell into a well.\n<span>\n<br></span>\n\nMany people saw the incident so they came to save him. Unfortunately no \none could enter the well to bring him out. Later, a smart man came up \nwith a bright idea to throw the man a strong rope to try to pull him out\n the well.\n<span>\n<br></span>\n\nWhen the rope reached\u00a0 and hit the man\u2019s head, he shouted angrily: \u201cDon&#039; bother me! Pick your own well, I am bathing.\u201d\n<br>\n\nDo you get the point why that short passage can be labeled as a spoof \ntext? Before we are going to go further, Let&#039;s see its rough translation\n to help you to\u00a0 get better understanding\n<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "apa-artinya-shawty-182",
            "question": "Apa artinya shawty ?",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "shawty itu bahasa slang-nya bhs inggris yang artinya cantik,menarik.<br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "biografi-aknes-monica-654",
            "question": "Biografi aknes monica",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Nama lahir\nAgnes Monica Muljoto\n\n\nNama lain\nAgnez Mo<br>\u00a0 \u00a0Lahir\n1 Juli 1986 (umur\u00a027)<br> Jakarta, Indonesia\n<br>\u00a0 Jenis Musik\nPop, R&amp;B\n<br>\u00a0 Pekerjaan\nPenyanyi, aktris, penari, presenter, pencipta lagu, perancang busana, bintang iklan\n\n\nInstrumen\nVokal<br><br>semoga membantu",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "nama asli: agnes monica muljoto\u00a0<br>tanggal lahir: 01, juli 1986 di jakarta indonesia\u00a0<br>terkena\u00a0sejak merilis debut album anak anak \" si meong\"( 1992)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "narrative-text-yang-bagus-dan-jarang-di-dengar-orang-797",
            "question": "Narrative text yang bagus dan jarang di dengar orang??",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "The story snow white<br>In earlier times there lived a , who named Snow White . He lived with his aunt and uncle because his parents died . One day she heard her uncle and aunt talking about leaving Snow White in the castle because they wanted to go to America and they did not have enough money to take Snow White with them . princess Snow White did not want her uncle and aunt to do this . So he decided to escape .<br><br><span>\u00a0The next day he ran away from home when her aunt and uncle were having breakfast , he fled into the wood . In the wood she felt very tired and hungry . Then she saw this cottage . She knocked but no one answered her so she went inside and felt asleep Meanwhile seven dwarfs came home from his work . They get into . There, they found Snow White woke up from his sleep . He saw the dwarfs . The dwarf said : \" What is your name ? &#039; Snow White said , \" My name is Snow White . \" One dwarf said , \" If you want , you can stay here with us . &#039; Snow White tells all about her story . Then daughter snow and the seven dwarves are now living happily ever after .</span>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "there-care-many-reasons-for-keeping-dogs-as-pete-in-the-city-area-554",
            "question": "There care many reasons for keeping dogs as Pete in the city area, but many peo- ple feel that keeping pet dogs should not be allowed In the city. Dogs are often not taken care properly. They are kept in small backyards and rarely taken for walks. They are left in the yard all day by themselves while the family rune work. Very little attention is given to the dog and it is not a very good life for it. It is no wonder why these dogs bark and disturb the neighbours and become a nuisance to the community.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 On the other hand, not all people treat their dogs this may and why should the peo- ple receive a lot of pleasure and enjoyment from dog's stifle'? Dogs can make a lonely person's life happy or make wonderful play- mate. It can also teach a child responsibility as they not only Potts lay with the dog, but also need to exercise, feed, and care for the dog.\u00a0\u00a0\u00a0 I feel that we should be allowed to keep dogs in the city, because ills is taken care of properly, dogs can be a great source of pleasure. As a child / used to enjoy playing and taking care of my pet. There is not greater loyalty a nelson can get than from a well-caned dog.\u00a0    1. Some people do not like the presence of pet dogs In their surroundings because ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are left in the yards\u00a0 \r\n(B) the dogs are often neglected \r\n(C) the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours \r\n(D) the dogs play with the owner's child \r\n(E) the dogs guard the security of the enyit onrnent\u00a0 \r\n\r\n2. The main idea of the last paragraph is ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) pet dogs are loyal animals \r\n(B) pet dogs are more loyal than humans \r\n(C) dogs can be a great source of pleasure \r\n(D) the writer has no objection to keeping dogs In the city \r\n(E) the writer used to play and took care of his pet when he was a child\u00a0 \r\n\r\n3. We can infer from the text that keeping pet dogs in the city will not cause any problem as long ....\u00a0\u00a0 \r\n(A) the dogs are amusing \r\n(B) the neighbours like having pet dogs \r\n(C) the dogs do not balk at the neighbours \r\n(D) the writer has succeeded in persuading the neighbours \r\n(E) its presence does not disturb the neighbourhood",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "1.c.the dogs often bark and disturb the neighbours<br>2.c.dogs can be a great source of pleasure<br>3.e.it&#039;s presence does not disturb the neighbourhood<br>ini menurut jawaban saya :)",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "coba-sebeutkan-contoh-dari-spoof-dan-kesimpulannya-845",
            "question": "Coba sebeutkan contoh dari spoof dan kesimpulannya",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Contoh :<br>Joe&#039;s Mother got angry because her son got a low mark on English test.<br>\n\"Why did you get such a low mark on that test?\" Asked mother angrily. \nAsked by his angry mother, Joe just kept silent and went out.<br>\nA few moment, Joe came back home and met his mother again. His mother asked the same question.<br>\nJoe answered steadily, \"Because of absence.\"<br>\n\"You mean you were absent on the day of the test?\" Mother wondered.<br>\nJoe replied, \"No, but the kid who sits next to me was.\"\n\n<br><br>Kesimpulan :<br><span><span>sebuah teks yang berisi tentang humor meski sebagian teksnya \nsudah dimodifikasi dari aslinya.</span></span><br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "bisa-gak-buatin-pidato-dari-teks-ini-plastic-surgery-is-not-s-r-624",
            "question": "Bisa gak buatin pidato dari teks ini\u00a0    plastic surgery is not s recent phenimenon, but it was appeared since 3000 years ago. in the past, it was for medical purpose but now it is creating beuty and trend to modify some part of body.\r\nmany people nowaday want to be extraordinary such as animal or less human by plastic surgery. they modifying their faces and bodies to make them more animal like. meny so called 'lizard people' have had their tongues split. a woman who changed her face like a cat. other people gone beyond different kinds of tattoos.\r\nthe people who done outcast actually they lack self respect and have adesperate need for attention. they should be treated by psychiatrist, not plastic surgeons. and we should be aware of society that no longer wants to look human",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "hi people, today i will tell you about plastic surgery. plastic surgery appeared 3000 years ago, in the past, it was for medical purpose but now it is only for a change of appearance. many people nowdays want to have a beautiful or handsome face, in other words &#039;being closer to perfections in the matter of appearance&#039;. but some people have some really weird tastes and they tried to be less human-like, by using plastic surgery, they tried to looks like a lizard or cats, and many other animals. the people that took plastic surgery is usually people who is not satisfied with their looks, or their body. they degraded\u00a0the gods creation, and try to be more &#039;perfect&#039;, however they sometime did not look at the risk. you see, if the surgery failed, then can you even imagine what your body or face would look like? and because of that i highly recommend not to take plastic surgery, and appreciate what god has given to us.\u00a0\u00a0<br><br>^aku tambahin beberapa informasi\u00a0",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "tolong-jelaskan-cara-menggunakan-linking-verb-272",
            "question": "Tolong jelaskan cara menggunakan LINKING VERB",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "penggunaan Linking verbs berfungsi sebagai kata (kerja) penghubung antara subjek dengan keterangannya.<br>example: The kids\u00a0<strong>act</strong> foolish.<br><br><strong>Act</strong> dalam kalimat itu adalah contoh linking verb.<br><br>semoga bisa membantu ^_^,,,<br>maaf kalau ada yang salah ^_^,,,",
                    "attachments": []
                },
                {
                    "answer": "<span>penggunaan Linking verbs berfungsi sebagai kata (kerja) penghubung antara subjek dengan keterangannya.<br>example: The kids\u00a0act foolish.</span><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "definisi-positive-adjective-itu-apa-dan-contohnya-569",
            "question": "Definisi positive adjective itu apa ?? dan contohnya ???",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "Definisi nya sudah diterangkan oleh mbak Karina, Yaitu berfungsi untuk menambahkan keterangan kata benda (noun),\u00a0 saya menambahkan contohnya saja <br><br>He has beautiful garden = adjective -&gt; beautiful noun nya garden<br><br>He has sharp eyes = adjective -&gt; sharp dari noun eyes<br><br>He loves to paint beautiful home -&gt; adjective beautiful dari noun home <br><br>",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        },
        {
            "slug": "buatlah-1-contoh-recount-text-732",
            "question": "Buatlah 1 contoh recount text",
            "attachments": [],
            "answers": [
                {
                    "answer": "last holiday i went to my grandparents house. me and my family went to a mall",
                    "attachments": []
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}